Two sisters advertise to get their dad a date...and get a whole lot more.
Billboard Dad is a comedy, family, tv movie film directed by Alan Metter.
High above Hollywood Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen are playing Matchmakers!
One's a surfer.
The other's a high diver.
When these two sisters team up to find a new love for their newly single Dad,
it's a fun-loving, eye-catching California adventure gone wild.
Mary-Kate and Ashley star in this fabulously funny love-struck
comedy filled with crazy schemes and cool surprises.
Determined to find their Dad, Max, a new love, the girls paint a
personal ad on a giant billboard in the heart of Hollywood.
After a few disastrous dates, Max finally meets
Brooke and it's love at first sight.
There's just one hitch, her unruly skateboarding son is the girls' arch rival.
Now, with the girls plotting every action-packed step of the way,
they've got to find out if love really does conquer all.
Full of outrageous events, mixed-up matches and lots of laughs, Billboard Dad tops the
charts as Mary-Kate and Ashley's coolest mischief-making adventure ever!
Tess Tyler, played by Mary-Kate Olsen.
Emily Tyler, played by Ashley Olsen.
Maxwell Tyler, played by Tom Amandes.
Brooke Anders, played by Jessica Tuck.
Nigel, played by Carl Banks.
Debbie, played by Ellen Ratner.
Billboard Dad is a 1998 American romantic comedy film directed by
Alan Metter starring Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen.
It was produced by Warner Bros.
in collaboration with Dualstar Productions and Tapestry Films (now Screendoor).
The film explores themes of matchmaking, los
angeles, california, twins, single father.
The tone is lighthearted.